<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyStoryBookApp</string>
    
    <string-array name="title_story">
        <item>I Found A Frog </item>
        <item>A Dog On A Log </item>
        <item>Bully Bill </item>
        <item>The Tooth Fairy </item>
        <item>A Trick Trike </item>
        <item>The Naughty Monkey </item>
        <item>Pirates Cove </item>
        <item>Samatha,The Girl Scientist </item>
        <item>The Homeless Monkey </item>
        <item>The Flower Garden </item>
        <item>story </item>
        <item>story12 </item>
        <item>story13 </item>
        <item>story14 </item>
        <item>story15 </item>
        
        
        
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="details_story">
        <item>Even though I have grandchildren of my own, it seems like it was only yesterday
when I returned home from school to find a frog in my bedroom.My mother just chuckled when I yelled out, “I found a frog on my bed.”
Now, she knew that I would eventually find one but she let me discover a wonder of Nature that many people miss.You see, a little earlier that spring, when I was 6 years old; I saw some little,
black fish in a pond.Since I didn’t have any pets I went home and asked my mother if I could have one.After we talked about my catching some of the fish I saw, and the responsibility of having a pet, she agreed.She gave me a bowl, told me to go catch a few, and said that while
I was out she would prepare their new home.
Off I went.There were so many that they were easy to catch.I filled the bowl and ran home.When I got home, my mother had an old fish bowl filled with water sitting on the corner of my desk.She asked to see the fish, looked, and with a big smile said,
“Tadpoles. – Wow! You are in for a surprise.”I asked what she meant and she just said that I would have to
wait and see, but to watch my fish carefully.After a few weeks, I noticed some were changing. “Mom,” I yelled with excitement. “Come here, my fish are growing legs.” She came into my room, looked, smiled, and told me to keep watching.After several more weeks, there were more changes. “Mom,” I yelled with excitement. “Come here, my fish are growing front legs and their tail is going away.”A week or so later when I got up, I was amazed. There were more changes.
My fish didn’t have tails, their legs were bigger, and they didn’t look like
the little black fish I had caught earlier in the Spring.That day, when I returned home from school, is when I yelled out, “I found a frog on my bed.”“Surprise,” yelled mom. “You watched a miracle right before your eyes. A fish
changed into a frog.Off I went. </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item>Bill is on a bullying spree. He believes that he is the strongest animal on the farm and that gives him the right to do as he pleases. But the farm animals decide to stop him in his tracks by …………….. a great tale that moves at a quick pace, keeping the reader engrossed right to the end.Farmer Fred had just bought a new bull. He named him Bill. Bill was a strong and handsome bull with great horns. He was very big for his age. Farmer Fred got Bill, the bull loaded into the trailer, and headed back home to his farm. When they arrived, Farmer Fred said, “Bill, welcome to your new home.” Bill just snorted and tossed his head back to show off his impressive horns.
This was all new to Bill as he was raised in a small stall and his new home was very different. He had a lot to explore. Bill stood on the hill and watched all the barnyard animals. He thought to himself. “I am the biggest animal on Farmer Fred’s farm. No other animal has such great horns.”Bill chuckled at the chickens as he slowly walked up to them. They were so small and they didn’t have horns.  As Bill approached, the chickens clucked. The lone duck, ducked, as Bill almost stepped on her.
Bill lowered his head and quickly shook it from side to side right in front of the chickens. “I’m Bill, the bull and I’m bigger than you chubby chickens,” he said in a deep voice. “And I am the boss of the barnyard.” Bill, the bull, frightened the chickens. They rapidly ran, flipped, flopped and, flew, to the safety of their cozy coupe. This made Bill, the bull, laugh loudly. He was having fun.Bill saw some plump pigs moving in the mud and decided to play a prank.
As he approached, he said loudly, “I heard Farmer Fred say that he needed some bacon for breakfast and ham for dinner.” He then laughed loudly and tossed his head around showing off his great horns.This frightened many of the pigs and they proceeded to their pen for protection.
The biggest pig, named Pork Chop, walked up to Bill and said.\n“You are a very mean bull, Bill.” Bill snorted a reply. “Well, you have a big, flat nose, a tornado tail and pink ears. Also, you are dirty, and smelly” Then Bill lowered his head, snorted a great snort,and shook his horns at Pork Chop.Pork Chop was a wise old pig and knew what Bill was doing. He wouldn’t be bullied by any bull, even Bill. Now, Bill, the bullying bull, was expecting Pork Chop to mush through the mud and proceed to the pen for protection. But Pork Chop just stood there looking at him. Then Pork Chop said in a soft voice.
“You are a very mean bull, Bill,” and walked awayThen, Bill saw some sheep in the meadow. Bill began to walk across the big barnyard towards them. When he got there, he was met by the Roger Ram, the leader of the flock.“I’m Roger Ram, rejoicing at meeting my newest neighbor on Farmer Fred’s farm,” he said in a very polite manner. Bill ran at Roger Ram, snorting and shaking his big horns and said, “I am Bill, the bull.I am the boss of the barnyard.”In a split second, Roger Ram, rammed Bill the bullying bull, between his big horns.Bill, the bullying bull, looked at Roger Ram and said. “All that white curly hair, might give you lots of flair, but you ram like a ewe.” Then Bill backed up, started to paw at the ground with his hefty hooves, snorted seven snorts, shook his horns, lowered his now lumpy head, and…………Roger Ram and the others retreated from the meadow. Bill, the bullying bull, was proud of what he had done.
All the barnyard animals were afraid of Bill. He was either threatening them with his size and big horns or making fun of the way they looked. It was not a pleasant day on Farmer Fred’s farm. “I am going to call him Bully Bill,”
said Henrietta Hen.“That’s not nice,” responded Roy Rooster. “It’s being a bully yourself.”
“Well, we will work on something to stop his bullying,” replied Toby Turtle.
Roger Ram said, “I don’t know what we can do? I rammed him and he called me a ewe.”Dorothy Duck said, “He almost stepped on me with those heavy hooves. No one is safe!” With tears in her eyes, little Patty Piglet said, “I heard, I was going to be eaten by Farmer Fred. I’m scared.” Pork Chop said in a soft and soothing tone, “Don’t worry my friends. By the evening feed by Farmer Fred, Bill, the bullying bull, will become our buddy.”Bill was having so much fun. He certainly was the boss of the barnyard.
He looked around and saw a big barn, with open doors, and he just had to let whoever lived there know that he was boss of the barnyard. It was a bright sunny day but as Bill walked into the dark barn, he couldn’t see anything.
This frightened him a little. He turned the corner around the door and … BOOM … he was stopped in mid stride. Bill realized that he had just walked into something really big. So big, it didn’t move when he walked into it.
As Bill’s eyes adjusted to the darkness in the barn, he started to see what had stopped him. He was looking at the chest of some big animal. Bill was scared.
As he looked up, he could see the biggest bull, with the biggest horns, staring down at him. A voice like thunder filled the barn. “I finally get to meet Bill, the boss of the barnyard.”Now Bill didn’t know what to do or what to say. All he could do was look up at this giant and wonder what would happen next. There was silence in the barn for several minutes as Bill just looked up in amazement. Finally, the big bull said something.
“I am Brian Bull and have lived on Farmer Fred’s farm for many, many, years. In all those years, never have the other animals asked me for help.But today, they came to me with the story of a big bull that was bullying them and they asked me to put an end to it. I agreed!” Bill was never, ever, so frightened. Brian could toss him across the barnyard, with little effort, and one push from his head. Brian slowly lowered his head. Bill looked down and began to shake. Brian got closer and whispered into Bill’s ear.“What do you think I should do, Bill? I promised the other animals I would put a stop to your bullying.”
“I have never been so frightened in my life and I know how the other animals must have felt.” Bill began to sob a little.“I now know how it feels to be bullied and you didn’t even really bully me. I have learned my lesson and I will go out and apologize to all the animals and ask them to forgive me“You don’t have to,” Brian said. “You already have.” As Bill turned around, he saw all the other animals standing in the doorway.“Here pig-pig-pig, come on chick-chick ….” The animals heard Farmer Fred calling them for the evening feed.Pork Chop walked over to Bill and said. “Come on, buddy. Let’s eat.”
 </item>
        <item>Deep in the New Forest where no big people ever went there was a tiny little magical village called the Ordon Gardens. Here, three little tooth fairies named Incisor, Canine and Molar were busy at work in their factory. The three tooth fairies were all named after types of teeth.Incisor was tall and skinny with short pink hair, Canine was also tall with blue hair and Molar was the short, wise one with curly, silver locks.
All day long the busy little fairies cleaned and shined the children’s milk teeth they had collected during the night.
The milk teeth were used to make very useful things in the Ordon Gardens like roads in the village and furniture in the homes for the little fairies.One day Incisor realised that the teeth coming into the cleaning factory were not as strong as they used be.
“Oh dear!” said Incisor “These teeth are fragile and brittle, with holes and black spots. They crumble as soon as I try to polish them with my cloth. Whatever are we to do?”“Yes.”said Canine “I know exactly what’s wrong, The children are beginning to eat far too many sweets and are not looking after their teeth at all.” “I know…we can fix it!” Said Molar the wise one. She sounded quite excited by her grand idea.The three fairies looked at each other and waited while Molar explained all. As usual, it was a fabulous idea. The three of them wasted no time at all and got to work straight away.

That night, it was Canine’s turn to fly off and collect all the milk teeth from under the sleeping children’s pillow. Off she flew with a bag of coins, some white berry sandwiches for her lunch and a pack of cards which the three fairies had spent all afternoon preparing.It was such a treat to leave the forest and see the city skyline but it was a dangerous place for fairies. Canine had to make sure that the big people never saw her.She flew through the starry sky and saw the wonderful city fast asleep.
Her first stop was a young boy named Junior.Earlier in the night Junior and his mum had placed his milk tooth under the pillow. Mummy tucked Junior into bed and told him all about the tooth fairy who would leave some money in exchange for his tooth. She gave him a goodnight kiss and left him to fall asleep.By the time Canine arrived, Junior was fast asleep. She flew in through the top window that was ajar and glided quickly down to Junior’s pillow. She perched beside him and braced herself in preparation for the task…“Heave……..” she lifted the pillow and wedged herself between the pillow and the bed. She quickly grabbed the tooth and tossed it over to her backpack.She placed two coins and the fairy’s special card in exchange under the
pillow and flew off into the night sky to find more milk teeth.In the morning, as soon as Junior woke up, he rummaged under the pillow to see if the tooth fairy had left any money for him.
He was thrilled to find the coins but looked blankly at the card he found in his hand. Mummy didn’t mention anything about a card…he wondered.Back in the village of Ordon Gardens, the fairies were very happy about the new information card they were giving to the children. Soon enough the milk teeth coming into the factory were strong and healthy again.
 </item>
        <item>Little Ross was sad. He didn’t have a nice new tricycle like all the other children. All he had was an old hand-me-down trike. After sulking he decided to do something about it and made a “trick trike” that was the envy of the neighborhood. It was the first day of Spring and everyone was out riding their nice new shiny tricycles that they got for Christmas.That is everyone but Ross.Ross didn’t get a nice new shiny tricycle but he did get his sisters old trike.
Ross was sad. Not only was the trike not new and shiny - it was rusty.
How could he ever ride that with all the other boys?Ross didn’t get a nice new shiny tricycle but he did get his sisters old trike.Ross looked at the boys riding their nice new shiny trikes.Then he looked at the old hand-me-down that was now his.He pushed the trike into a corner of the garage and slowly walked into the house“What’s wrong?” his mommy asked. “You should be outside riding your trike with the other boys.”Well, that almost brought poor Ross to tears.Then he explained to his mommy that the trike …wasn’t new,wasn’t shiny,wasn’t nice …and it is rusty!Right away Ross’s mommy understood what was bothering him.He was embarrassed to ride his sisters’ old trike, especially when everyone else had a new one.She looked at Ross and said. “Let’s spend a fun day together. Follow me to the garage sport; we are going to Trick Your Trike!”Ross didn’t know what she meant but in a matter of minutes he found out.The rest of the day Ross and his mommy were busy in the garage.They took the trike apart, piece-by-piece.They painted it bright red with orange and yellow flames on the fenders.They polished the handlebars, tires, pedals, and wheels.They painted, rubbed, scrubbed, buffed, and polished each-and-every piece.Neither one of them could wait until it was put back together.Piece-by-piece, part-by-part Ross and his Mommy put the trike back together.
When they were done, they were both amazed.Right in front of them was a one-of-a-kind tricycle, a truly beautiful Trick Trike.Ross hugged his Mommy and thanked her for all her help.She smiled and told Ross she really enjoyed spending the day with him.“Now go and ride with your friends,” she said.As Ross road down the street, his Mommy heard the other boys saying:“What a great trike!”“Where did you get that?”“Wow! Look at the trike Ross has!”
“Can I get one?”“Want to trade?”She knew Ross was very happy.THE END
 </item>
        <item>Ashley ,the Rabbit has three new friends!  They are Sophie, Josh and Tom.  Today she is playing with Sophie in the garden behind Sophie’s house.“Are you dry today, Ashley?” asks Sophie.  She is making a joke about the day Ashley fell in the pond in the park.  “Yes, I am dry today,” smiles Ashley.  “Thank you for helping me to get out of the pond.”Sophie and Ashley are sitting under a big tree at the back of the garden.  Plop!  Something falls down from the tree.  “What was that?” asks Ashley.  “I don’t know,” answers Sophie.Plop!  Plop!  It happens again two times!  “Look at this,” says Sophie.  Ashley moves closer to Sophie.  Sophie is pointing at something.  Ashley looks at it.  It’s a banana peel!They look around the ground.  They find two more banana peels.  Plop!  It’s another banana peel.   But this time it drops down right on top of Sophie’s head.  Yuk!Sophie and Ashley hear someone laughing.  They look up into the tree and what do they see?  It’s a monkey.  It’s a very naughty monkey.  It’s Baba, the Monkey!“Hey, you, up there!” says Sophie. “What are you doing?” But Baba does not answer;
he only laughs. Plop! He drops another
banana peel. This time it drops
on Ashley’s head!Sophie and Ashley are not happy. This is a very naughty monkey. Why is he dropping banana peels down to the ground? Why is he dropping
banana peels on top of their heads?“You come down here right now!” says Ashley. “Yes,” says Sophie. “You must help us clean up this mess.” But Baba just laughs. Now
he starts to swing from branch to branch. Oops!He misses a branch.  He falls to the ground.  Plop!  But this time it’s not a banana peel.  This time it’s a naughty monkey.  He’s not moving.  Oh, no!  Is Baba hurt?Sophie and Ashley are scared They are not happy about the banana peels. But they don’t want Baba
to be hurt They run over to see if Baba is okay
He is on his back.
They look down at him.He jumps up and laughs and runs around in circles.  He is not hurt  He was just pretending to be hurt  He runs and jumps and does cartwheels and somersaults. Sophie and Ashley laugh at Baba.  He is a naughty monkey, but he is also a very funny monkey.   “My name is Baba!” he says as he runs around.  “I’m Sophie and this is Ashley,” says Sophie.Sophie and Ashley start to run around with Baba. Now they try to chase him, but he is too fast. He runs around the tree and they follow him. He looks behind him and does not see
the banana peel on the ground.Baba slips on the banana peel.  His feet go way up into the air.  Plop!  He lands on his back again.  This time Sophie and Ashley sit on top of Baba.  He can’t move now!Why are you sitting on top of me? shouts Baba.  Let me go!  Let me go!  We can’t let you go until you answer a question. says Ashley.  Yes, says Sophie.  Why do you drop banana peels?“I don’t know,” laughs Baba. “I don’t know what to do with the peels after I eat the bananas.” “But this is not good,”
says Sophie. “We don’t want banana peels in our garden.”“You’re right,” says Baba.  “I’m sorry.  I made a mess and now I must clean it up.”  So Baba starts to pick up banana peels.  There are many banana peels, so Sophie and Ashley help Baba.Now the garden is clean.  “Thank you for helping to pick up banana peels,” says Sophie.  “Let’s  have a snack.  What do you want to eat?”  “How about a banana split?” says Baba.
 </item>
        <item>The bottom of the sea opened and the waters began draining. The waters started going round and round. Slowly at first, and then picking up speed until we were in a whirlpool. It didn’t take long for the swirling waters to suck the Seahorse to the bottom of the sea. As for us in the longboat, we watched her go down as we spiraled around that whirlpool before getting sucked down with her.Arrgh! It makes me heart happy to see that lad growing like he is. They call him Sandy, after me. Ya see I’m his Great-Great-Great-Grandpa.” “Sandy,” called his mom from the house. “You forgot you chores for the day. Remember you were going to clean the attic.”“Oh,” grumbled Sandy as he slowly walked to the house. “I don’t mind chores, but cleaning the attic! There hasn’t been anyone up there in years.”“It must be dark, dirty, and full of spiders and other creepy things. There is probably even a ghost or two living up there with the spiders.”“I unlocked the door to the attic,” his mom said. “Be careful, it’s a little dark and there is a lot of stuff just lying around or stacked in piles.”The spirit of Sand-dollar thought to himself as he watched Sandy.
 “Arrgh, I must have looked the same on that stormy night when I hid me treasure map in that very room. I wonder if it will be finally found.”“This isn’t so bad,” Sandy said to himself. “There’s a lot of neat stuff up here. I’ll clean as I move and organize all these different things.” “Arrgh,” Sand-dollar thought to himself. “That lad be a hard worker. I’d have him on me crew if I could. He’s only been up here a few hours and he’s almost done.”This Book taught him, how to hide the treasure. As instructed in the book, he took all the treasure the gold, silver,the jewels, and buried them.
He asks that whoever finds this other treasure share it, do good, and do what the Book says. “Wow,” said Sandy.“Quite a story,” Sandy’s mom said.
 </item>
        <item>“Hi! My name is Samantha and I want to be a scientist. You may be wondering why and my answer is simple. I am amazed at all the wonderful things like television, cellular phones, men on the Moon, space exploration, and the list goes on. But those are big things and I just don’t understand everything about them yet. I also wonder about smaller things like-why do my doll’s eyes close when I lay her down and open when I pick her up. Or how are cartoons made? Hmm – I know it has something to do with Science. My brother Samuel wants to be a scientist too, but he likes things that I don’t, like-why Stalactites grow.
But even though we don’t like the same things it’s still Science so we get along just fine.
In fact, our teachers help us better understand Math, technology, current events and trends - all of which are important. We even help each other and have lots of fun.I like to experiment or take things apart to see how they work. No matter what I do, I tell my mom or dad what I am going to be doing and sometimes even ask for their help. I would never just do something. I could get hurt.  Sometimes it’s best to start small, and that’s just what I did. I remember my first experiment in detail and it was a lot of fun to do. I had to do an optical illusion. You may be wondering why that is important and all I can say is that it’s the basis for making
cartoons - and here is why. Our brains fill in the gaps for whatever our eyes aren’t processing. So two different pictures can actually become one or still images can appear to be moving.Try this experiment, it’s lots of fun and there is nothing dangerous about it. Here is what you need:That is Science! Have some fun and try different pictures.(I even put Samuel in jail once). Hey, do you want to do a little magic and make a spot on a piece of paper disappear? It’s different for each person but it does disappear. Yes, it’s Science too but let’s get to the experiment and I’ll explain the Science later.
 </item>
        <item>Once upon a time, there lived a monkey who had no home of his own. They called him ‘Springs’, for he always walked with a bounce in his steps.He had sold everything he owned, and with that money, he had started traveling the world.He wanted to see the world’s smallest and biggest wonders. He traveled from village to village, town to town,and offered his services- to do work in exchange for food and shelter.He was a happy monkey and he loved helping people.One day, he passed through the village of Zver, where twenty animals lived. He saw an old beaver. so he walked towards him and said “Hello, Mr. beaver. If I was to do some garden work for you today, would you be so kind as to give me something to eat.”The old beaver agreed and asked Springs to do some gardening and fix up a few things around the house. It was a long and tiring day for Springs but enjoyed his day. When springs returned to the house in the evening, the whole village had gathered there. There was a lot of food put out on the large wooden table and everybody was celebrating as though a hero had come to their small village.They all had a great time that night; it was like a big party. There was dancing and lots food and Springs really enjoyed his evening.
The following morning when Springs was ready to leave, the old beaver approached Springs with tears in his eyes and said, “Thank you for joining us for dinner.
Please come back whenever you have time. I have two boys around your age who I have not seen in 10 years. Spending time with you reminded me of my boys.”Springs did not know what to say so he just hugged the Beaver, just like he would his father, and set off on his way with a promise to return one day.Springs had been walking for some time and was tired.He saw two highway robbers who pushed him down and took his bag away. When the robbers looked in his bag they only found a rope, some tools, and some bread. They threw his bag on the ground and ran away. Springs picked up his backpack and continued on his journey.He started to think about all the good and bad in the world. The road was long and winding and finally led him to a dark forest. The only way he could continue his journey was to walk through the forest. Springs walked for more than an hour and then he realised he was lost. He decided to climb up a tree to relax and eat some of the bread the villagers had given him. Suddenly Springs heard some voices shouting for help.He climbed down from the tree and ran in the direction the voices were coming from. Springs reached the place the voices were coming from.Springs reached the place the voices were coming from. He saw that the two robbers who had pushed him earlier that day were trapped inside a deep hole in the ground. They were both trapped and couldn’t get out, and were yelling for help.Springs quickly reached into his backpack and grabbed the rope that was inside. He tied one end of the rope to a tree and threw the other end inside the hole. The robbers both quickly climbed up the rope to safety.The robbers were amazed that Springs had saved them. One robber asked “Why did you help us? We pushed you and tried to rob you earlier!”.Springs replied “There are good people and bad people in this world. The good people do good things and bad people do bad things. I have decided to be one of the good people.” The two robbers were amazed by Springs’ reply.Springs told the robbers, “I have traveled far and wide, seen happiness as well as sorrow. I have met all kinds of people; good, bad, old, and young. I have experienced all sorts of bad things, but I have always tried to do only good things.”As Springs was leaving, he gave the two robbers some bread with a smile and said, “I hope what I have said today will help you realize that there is always a way to live without causing harm to others.”
 </item>
        <item>Rose and Violet laughed when they realized how silly they had acted. Of course, the presents would be identical, just like them. They each got a box unwrapped, opened, and then looked inside. Rose happily yelled, “Stuff to make a flower garden. This is great, something I always wanted to do. I can grow my own flower garden.”Violet said, “I like flowers, and a garden would be nice. But there’s a lot of stuff in this box and it seems like it would be a lot of work.” Violet was right. There was a lot of stuff in the box.It contained everything they needed to make a flower garden, everything except water, sunshine, and love. Both girls thanked their mom and dad for the great present and they dragged their heavy boxes outside to start their gardens.
They each selected a patch of ground to call her own, took the “How To Garden” book from the box, and began to read. Rose said, “Violet, you were right. This is going to be a lot of work.”They carefully removed the grass, loosened up the ground, added and mixed in the special flower soil, and planted their flower seeds. Violet found some nice sticks and pretty ribbon to make a fence around her garden. She gave the seeds their first watering and said, “Rose, I am going inside to watch television.”
Rose asked her Dad to help her make a stone fence around her garden.
“A very special garden needs a very special fence,” she said to him as they gathered and placed the stones. After some time the fence was completed and Rose gave the seeds their first watering.I’ll plant the ones I pull from my garden into Violets. And that is exactly what she did. Rose then gave both gardens a big drink of water. She loved her garden and there was no reason she shouldn’t love her sister’s equally.
Oh! It wouldn’t be long now. It wouldn’t be long before there were two beautiful flower gardens. The girls were so excited. They just couldn’t wait to see all the colorful flowers. The next morning they got dressed and hurried outside to tend their gardens. To their surprise, they were in full bloom. They shrieked with excitement, held hands, and danced in circles. The flowers were so beautiful.
Every color in the rainbow was in their gardens. </item>
        <item>story </item>
        <item>story12 </item>
        <item>story13 </item>
        <item>story14 </item>
        <item>story15 </item>
    </string-array>
    
    
</resources>